Here is wise man Daniel moving in the midst of the SCOAN's congregation,
and praying for the people in the power of the Holy Ghost.
The lightning of God flows through the faculties of wise man Daniel to expose all the darkness
in the lives of people.
As he moves in the congregation, he encounters this lady who instantly reacts as the light of God
exposes the darkness in her life.
Let's watch the encounter.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
All over your body, fire in the mighty name of Jesus!
You can't resist it.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus! All over your body. Speak out, who are you!
What is your mission?
Daniel! So, you are among the five people that have been disturbing my kingdom!
You have been tormenting my kingdom! Where are my queens and princesses?
They are missing; I can't find them. Daniel, why is it?
I called your master the other day. I want to ask you a question.
What have we done to you? Why are you fighting us?
We are not fighting you but you are fighting us. Why?
My queens, princesses and kings – I can't find them anymore.
There is no one to send a message or to go on an errand for me. Why?
Who are you?
I am the queen mother. We are many. I came myself; I came from my throne. Me, Osun.
You said you left your throne and came here?
Yes. I came myself to ask you a question. What is it? What have we done to you?
Why are you making me lose my queens, princesses and kings? Why?
Where are your princesses, kings, princes?
They came to this place and you collected them from me.
I can't find them anymore; I can't see them anymore.
There is no one to go on an errand for me.
Last month, you collected a big person from me, one of my big queens. Why?
This is a House of God. Demons have no place here. Your people are demons?
My people are demons.
My people are demons. Do we torment you? Why are you tormenting me?
Why are you tormenting the spirit of osun, the marine?
Why are you disturbing us?
Why are you disturbing the fishes, the big fish in the river and the snails? Why?
I said I called your master.
Physically or spiritually?
I called him on the phone physically.
You were in her and called. What did you say when you called?
I told him that he's battling my kingdom and I am ready for him.
He ordered me to come here and I came. Me, great osun, ezenwanyi.
Yes.
As a queen mother how do you operate in this body?
We are many in this body.
How many of you are in this body?
The spirit of the marine. This is the big fish that lives in the river Niger,
the spiritual husband and the idol spirit from her father's house.
You said this place was tormenting your kingdom.
Yes.
Arresting your queens, princes, princesses, and kings.
How is this place tormenting your kingdom?
This place? Any time that any of my queens, princesses or king come here,
before I know it, I see another light in them that I cannot go near. Why?
What is here that is arresting them?
What is here that is arresting your demons?
You know this. Why are you asking me? You know. Can't you see the light everywhere?
Where is the light?
Can't you see it?
You see it because you have four eyes – the physical eyes and the spiritual ones and you see it.
Why are you asking me? Can't you see the light of the Righteous Man everywhere? Can't you see it?
What is the light doing to your kingdom, you demon?
The light has been disturbing my kingdom.
I am losing my queens, princesses and kings every day, all the time.
OK, let's come to this body. What have you done to this body? The body of the lady you are occupying.
This body? I have destroyed her.
How?
I have destroyed this body.
She read Catering and Hotel Management.
After her graduation, she came to Lagos to look for a job.
I knew that any hotel she applied to as a chef, they would give her an appointment.
I used to go before her. Even when she did the practical, she would pass it.
They would give her an appointment letter.
I would go and incite their mind and they would look for one excuse to dismiss her
when she was supposed to resume for work.
When they do the test for her she would pass?
She would pass.
But on the appointment day, what you would do?
They would give her an appointment letter.
When it is that time, I would go there and cause hatred; they would dislike her.
Those who were supposed to employ her - you would possess them?
Exactly.
What would happen when you possess them?
They would dislike her.
Even though they initially asked her to come?
All of a sudden they would hate her?
Exactly.
How would she feel?
She would be crying.
How would you, queen mother, feel?
I would be very happy.
Secondly, I looked at her certificates that she was carrying up and down.
I sent floods to the house where she kept her credentials to spoil everything.
OK, right now, you demon - your end has come.
It is a right time - you leave this body.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
In the mighty name of Jesus.
Daniel.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Why are you touching my crown? Stop.
Useless crown.
Come out in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body - fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now go, in Jesus' name.
You are free. Rise up.
How are you?
Fine.
You are fine?
Yes.
You wanted to fight me here.
No.
You were trying to put your fingers into my eyes.
You said that you were the queen mother, a big fish inside the river Niger and an idol.
I don't know.
I know I used to dream about being in a big river, sitting down with my crown on my head
and people would bow down before me.
You called the church. Can you tell the reason why you called the man of God?
I don't know. I don't even know when I did it.
It is a friend of mine who told me that I had called.
I was kind of quarrelling with them that they were disturbing my kingdom.
When my friend told me this I didn't believe it.
You didn't know when you called?
That demonic crown, the demonic queen, queen mother is out of you.
The idol is out of you. The big fish is gone.
Live your life to please Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus.
Emmanuel! (God with us – Matthew 1:23)
My names are Chinasa Victoria Okorie.
I am from Ebonyi State, Nigeria.
The problems that brought me to the SCOAN, were a strong marine spirit and a spiritual husband.
Actually, I cannot say how the evil spirit entered me but I grew up with it.
My father is a man of God.
When I was still in primary school, Primary 1 and 2,
my dad used to tell me that I was possessed because of the way I behaved.
I wouldn't eat and could go for three days without tasting anything.
If you forced me to eat, it would be a problem.
I wasn’t happy and would always cry. I didn't want to play with anybody.
I liked to stay on my own and didn't want anybody to talk to me.
I even hated my mother, father and everybody around me.
I always wanted to sleep because when I slept, I would see myself with people I didn't know.
I enjoyed playing and eating with them; I was happy with them.
As time went on, my dad and mum really tried and took me to many places.
My dad being a man of God, invited all his prayer warriors, ministers, friends.
They tried to deliver me many times but during the deliverance,
I would just be laughing and looking at them.
It has been going like that.
They really tried and took me to many places.
Actually I was born and brought up in Ondo State, Akure.
They took me in Ondo and to other States for deliverance but it did not work.
From Primary 3 it continued until I entered Secondary School and when I was in JSS3,
they crowned me the queen of the ocean.
The celebration were so awesome – many people such as kings, princes,
governors and presidents from countries all over the world, were present there in the spiritual world that day.
They crowned me the queen that day.
They gave me powers in my eyes, mouth and hips.
Anything I say then as of...
If someone provoked me and I cried, a bad thing would happen to that person.
If a person provoked me and I said, "As you are going, a car will hit you!" -
it will not be more than five minutes before it happens.
My friends started calling me a witch and all kinds of names.
It continued like that until I was in SSS2 when they came to me.
I used to see them physically; if I sat down and wanted to see them, I would.
I used to talk to them.
My mum noticed that I would be talking but she would not see anybody talking to me.
She would ask me if I was mad and I would tell her to leave me alone,
that I was just thinking about something and she would leave me.
When I was in SSS2, they came to me physically and said that my parents were tormenting them,
that prayers of my parents were disturbing them
and that they were not giving me chance to accomplish my mission in this world.
They said I should come back to the other world by dying physically.
I agreed with them and said that it wasn’t a problem.
It was a Wednesday and they told me that they would come and fetch me by 2am and I agreed.
At around 12 midnight, they came and showed me many people
in the spiritual world, many great people, waiting to welcome me back.
They had cooked and everybody was at the party dancing.
I too was happy because I wanted to go back.
What really happened was that when I sat down, something told me, 'Victoria, what is wrong with you?
You have good parents, a caring mother and father.
Why don't you tell them that you are going, so that they can say goodbye?'
I agreed and thought that it wouldn’t be good for my parents to wake up in the morning and find my body.
They wouldn’t know where I went and could cry. My parents have been good.
For those out there who give birth to children and do not care about them,
if you really love and care for them, before they do anything, they'd tell you.
That was how I was led and went to my dad's room and knocked, my dad woke up and came out.
I asked him whether he knew that I loved him, he said that he did and that he also loved me.
I said, "Daddy, I am going back to where I belong."
My daddy asked me where did I belong and I told him that by 2am,
I was going back and he would not see me again but I would miss everybody - goodbye.
My dad was surprised and said he had married my mum in 1984
I was born in 1985 and he did not go anywhere to ask for a child
but that God had given me to them and that I did not belong anywhere else.
I then walked out on my dad.
My mum woke up, was annoyed, tied her wrapper and went to the church.
She walked up and down the church altar praying, I just looked at her and laughed.
My dad called his friends, pastors and prayer warriors.
They came and prayed for me but I laughed at them.
Actually that day, I died and did not know what was happening physically anymore.
When I got to the other world, they welcomed me, danced with me and everyone was happy with me.
I saw many great people I knew physically and also many other people did not know.
I saw many structures there.
Some people were half fish half human, while others were half snake half human.
Some were half crab half human. They welcomed me and we danced.
All of a sudden, the goddess screamed, "What is happening in my kingdom?"
She said, "Fire!" and called me saying, "Queen Vicky!"
I replied, "Yes, my goddess".
She said, "Can you see what your parents are doing to us?"
They opened my eyes and I could see my dad, mum and many other people firing prayer.
There was fire everywhere.
They took a cane flogged me and asked to go back.
That was how I came back. I saw my mummy, daddy and everyone crying and praying.
I came back to life.
What was the condition you were given on this earth that you must not do?
OK. After I came back, they told me that in that world I came to, I was married to a great person.
No man on earth, no mortal man is on the same level. No man wants to marry me.
At the age of 22 years, I would become a billionaire.
I will be rich and if I want to have kids, I can have kids
but I would never have a crown which means no man would be my husband;
that is, an earthly husband because I already had a husband there.
I said that there was no problem.
Suitors were coming for me but my parents said they wanted me to go to a higher institution,
they didn’t want me to marry.
As young as I was, suitors were coming.
Because my parents didn’t like it, I didn’t care.
That was how things had been going.
When I entered school, suitors started coming; everybody wanted to marry me.
My people advised my parents that I should marry and still go to school.
So, that was how I fell in love with somebody.
When I married this man…
On the day of my traditional wedding, all of them came and sat down.
They said, "Queen Vicky, we will show you" but I kept quiet,
"We will show you". I kept quiet.
If I danced, they would talk and I would stop dancing and be quiet.
Nobody knew what was wrong with me.
When I entered the marriage, they struck.
They entered through my husband and started tormenting me.
When I was pregnant, this man would always beat me.
There was no month I was not admitted to the hospital.
He would always beat me.
It was the grace of God that I delivered the child.
Two weeks after I had delivered my baby, he continued to beat me.
In the end, they scattered the marriage.
I left the marriage and went back to my parents.
I gave my baby to my parents and went back to school.
I'm sorry madam. When your husband was beating you, what were you seeing spiritually at that moment,
as the force behind him beating you?
Actually, I knew they were the ones doing it
but because I had gotten married, I had disconnected.
I still belonged but I couldn’t see anything.
They blinded my eyes, that was the punishment.
I didn’t see them but I knew that I was going there but they blinded my eyes.
What was the reaction of your husband, after he'd beaten you? How he would now feel?
The funny thing is that anytime my husband finished beating me,
if he saw any wound on my body, he would ask, "What have I done?"
He would start begging me and crying.
He would say, "I don’t know what came over me, it's like something entering me".
That was how I would believe him until the marriage broke up.
We can understand from our sister that because she broke the covenants,
when she got married to her husband, the spiritual forces from the marine world would enter him
to be beating her up physically.
After committing the act, he would immediately recover himself and wouldn't know
how he had been so violent to his wife.
This is a very important lesson for all of us, especially those of us who may be experiencing such
in our homes, to know that many times there are spirits involved is such activities.
Madam, you said that you broke up with your husband.
What eventually happened that you were able to reconnect with the marine world?
After I broke up, I went back to school and started praying again
but they were not happy so they attacked my son. They gave me many punishments.
When I finished school, they destroyed my certificate. Frustration everywhere.
I couldn’t concentrate and felt like dying.
One day, I went to a river and wanted to jump inside.
I said, "OK, come and take me, I want to come back. Why should you frustrate me?"
So, someone called me back.
After that, I met a friend who said he wanted to take me to a place, to a spiritualist.
When we got there, the spiritualist asked me if I didn't know whom I was.
I said, "I am who I am".
He told me that I shouldn't lie or pretend because I knew whom I was very well.
He said that the people what were supposed to protect me,
that my parents had chased them away and that my prayers chased them away.
He then said I would never have peace until I called them and begged them.
I asked how I would do it because I was already frustrated because I had no job and I didn't want
to involve myself in prostitution or in stealing.
Then, the spiritualist gave me a list of things to buy and that I should all those things take to the beach.
So, I bought the things and took them to the beach.
At the beach, I knelt down, begged them and reconciled with them.
When I slept in the night, I saw myself in their midst.
They said they had opened my eyes, that I would see everything.
Five months later, they said they wanted to initiate me as the queen mother, of the whole Africa.
So, they initiated me, crowned me and gave me powers.
They gave me double powers in my eyes.
I could be here and see what was happening in Ghana because I ruled as overall.
I had to monitor all the countries to see what was happening.
They gave me powers in my eyes, mouth and hips.
They have me power to give people wealth.
They gave me power to give people children.
OK madam. We want to take it step by step.
When you became the queen mother, as you said in the spiritual world, you mentioned you were given
some specific powers. We just want you say them one by one.
You mentioned first of all that you were able to give people wealth.
Can you explain exactly how you would go about that in a physical world?
I could actually give people wealth.
Actually, I would command, I wouldn't go for work.
I had queens, kings and people under me.
I would just give the command and they would do it.
I even dated someone that I gave wealth.
The wealth is...
My queens would bring their boyfriends and husbands for wealth.
If we would give you wealth, we would give you our rules and regulations.
Our rules said that you can be a millionaire or billionaire
but you were not allowed to give our money to charities, motherless homes or to a pastors.
You were not allowed to use the money to pay tithes.
Even if you mother is a child of God, you couldn’t give her,
neither your father or your younger ones, if they served God.
As far as they believed in God, you couldn’t give them.
Even if your mother was suffering, wearing slippers
and picking from the garbage, you shouldn’t give to your mother.
Any day you would do it, it is death.
Because before we...
How we do is...
If you come to us and said you needed wealth, we'd say, "No problem".
That is how we just call and...
If your girlfriend or wife came to our kingdom saying you needed wealth,
we would tell the person to wear white when they want to sleep in the night
because white is the symbol of the marine.
Everything you would wear would be white and then, you would sleep.
At the midnight, your spirit would then come to us and we would baptise you with blood.
How we got that blood was from the disobedient disciples.
Like me, they told me not to marry but I went and got married.
If not for the family I came from, they would have used my blood.
Let me just say that God is merciful.
That was the kind of blood we would use.
Any time you disobeyed us, we would kill you and your blood would be there.
OK. Our sister is explaining that the spiritual kingdom of darkness, the marine world had the power to give wealth
but conditions were attached, that such money could not be given to any church,
to any Christian, or for any form of charity.
Madam, those millionaires that were enriched by your kingdom, what would they be spending their money on?
Since you couldn’t spend your money on anything that belonged to God,
you could use it at the night clubs, give it to girls, use it to smoke and drink and do your normal business.
You were not allowed to use the money for good things.
You also mentioned you had the power to give children.
Can you explain more about this?
Yes, we gave children because in the marine world, if you came there,
we have different children – we have fish, snakes, crabs, pythons,
we have different animals that live in the sea and symbolise the spirits of the marine.
If anyone comes to us and says that they needed a child, no problem, we would give them.
We would send a fish or a snake to enter into the person's womb.
So, you will give birth but the child will definitely kill you
or give you problems and you would develop a heart attack.
That is why, you see some people during deliverances saying that they are a snake or fish.
People of God, we are listening to our sister.
We are really learning a lot from what she is saying.
This is someone who has a practical experience as someone who was part of that kingdom.
Now madam, do you mean to day that in this physical world, when you look around
because your spiritual eyes were opened, you were able to see those who were part of your kingdom?
Tell us about the kind of things you see, for an example; if you see people who are Christians -
what identifies them as a Christian, or those who are just claiming to be Christians?
Actually, with my own experience...
I had the power that wherever I went in this world,
anybody who had the spirit of marine, immediately I saw you, I would know.
Anybody who is a child of God, immediately I saw you, I would know.
Anyone who is a lukewarm Christian, immediately I saw you, I would know.
Anyone who is a bench warmer, immediately I say you, I would know.
They all have a sign. Like a children of God, a born again Christian,
the light is here and is very red. That is the sign of a real born again Christian.
The sign of a marine would be here and would be very white like a star.
When I see it, I would know that the person was our member.
A lukewarm Christian, the light would be there but it would be very small,
like a light that wants to die or quench.
A bench warmer would just be there and is very easy meat to eat.
Those bench warmers and lukewarm Christians - you were able to attack them very easily?
Yes, and the lukewarm Christians.
You mentioned specific powers you had in your eyes, your hips, your mouth.
Can you explain how you used those powers?
They put something in my body whereas I don’t love men.
Men love me. I don’t love.
What I do...
I used the power in my eyes since they crowned me the queen mother.
I don’t lust after men; I had girls that did that, it wasn’t my business.
I used the power in my eyes to control the whole Africa and to check what was happening everywhere.
The power in my mouth was authority – anything I said, would happen.
OK. Now madam, can you tell us, from your experience, what can you say about the states of the world
we are living in right now, compared to the amount of people who are under this bondage?
I would say because I know the signs...
Many people would be possessed and they would not know, while some people would know.
I knew my own very well.
Some people would not know; they are ignorant.
I am very sure that Christians should tighten their belts because if the rapture should place today,
I don't know about that...
OK. Our sister is saying that many people would be possessed but they don't know about it
because they are under that bondage without knowing about it, and that is the reason why
we are listening to this experience to open our eyes.
One more question madam.
What can you say concerning...
If you look at this world and you say that majority of people are under this bondage,
what specific things from the marine kingdom introduced to this world as a means of initiating people?
So the other can learn from this.
We have many things we produce. The marine world is a world of beauty.
It is a world of fashion.
We produce hair attachments, earrings, gold, clothes and flashy things.
I am not saying that every hair attachment is from the marine kingdom
but anything fashionable that will come to this world we will produce it first.
We bring out the samples. We have some of our agents here;
they will produce it, while some people are not agents but they just produce.
When you buy, for example, the sample of the hair attachment we brought
and you do not pray in the name and blood of Jesus -
it is good if you buy anything from the market, before you use it, to pray over it.
If you pray over it, the power on it spoils but if you do not pray over it and wear it,
you will start seeing yourself in the night eating in your dreams with strange faces or swimming.
Hair attachments, makeup, earrings, jewellery, clothes – fashion.
The way we enter through clothing is for example, a lady who did not have the spirit of lust before,
she would notice that she went to the market and bought clothes
and started feeling attraction when seeing a man
who did not even talk to her. She would start thinking of rubbish.
Immediately you wear those clothes, all over your body is written, 'lust'.
Men would begin to pursue you.
That is why you would see some people ending up prostituting and it is not their fault.
They don’t know the power behind it. You cannot blame them.
OK. People of God, our sister has said so much and we want everyone to take your lesson
from what she is saying. She made a very important point that any time you get something you must pray
in the name of Jesus Christ, in the blood of Jesus Christ before simply wearing it or putting it on.
I believe this message will help us to cultivate consciousness
in all that we are doing of God's presence.
Sister, we want you to tell us how you came to the SCOAN. What brought you here?
What brought me to the SCOAN was that my frustration was too much because I broke their covenant.
They said I should not get married; I got married and at the end, they scattered the marriage.
There are many covenants people make and they don’t know.
You would see a young girl who is very charming,
she has kids and is a billionaire but has no husband.
It is a covenant.
There are many covenants.
Somebody who just got married and it is up to a year before she dies;
it is a covenant. She had made a covenant.
There are plenty covenants like that.
Because I broke their covenant, they started to frustrate my life.
I went to school but they scattered my documents.
I had nothing to present.
I was frustrated.
They started making people to hate and frustrate me. Frustration was everywhere.
Apart from these challenges you were facing personally, in the kingdom you were in as a queen mother -
what was the effect that the SCOAN and the ministry of Prophet T.B. Joshua was having on those
who were part of your kingdom?
I really needed deliverance but I came to the SCOAN with two missions.
I came to be delivered. I knew that I needed deliverance.
There was fire on the mountain. My kingdom was shaking.
I was losing members every day. That was why I came.
A friend invited me to come here for deliverance and I came.
The day I came, I saw everything that was happening.
This one was saying, “I am a snake”. This one was saying, “I am a fish”.
I was thinking that it was arrant nonsense and an insult.
I was thinking, “Why should I stay here while all these children are saying,
‘I am a snake. I am a fish. I am this?’”
I became furious in my spirit; I was angry. I went home that day.
When the wise man came and touched me, I just looked at them.
I left.
When I came back another day, I knew that I needed deliverance
but when that spirit would come it would back me up.
The wise man came and touched me; I was calm.
He went away.
My people said to me, “queen mother, this is an insult. Why should this little boy touch your crown?"
So, I became annoyed.
That day, I was supposed to come back to this place but I went to my friend's place and slept there.
The following day, we would come to the church.
When I slept, I went to the marine kingdom and
saw many of my fish, snakes and crabs were dead; I had lost members.
I was annoyed. I came back to life.
You mean that those who had come to the SCOAN for deliverance, spiritually you would see that your fish
and snakes in your kingdom had died because the person had come and received the deliverance?
Yes.
If anyone comes to the SCOAN and is delivered, that spirit that is the fish would be dead in our kingdom.
That is how we would know that they have arrested one of our members.
We can really see the work of God here in the SCOAN. We give glory to God.
Finally madam, we know that you came and we saw how you were prayed for,
tell us what happened when you were prayed for by wise man Daniel.
That day, I just woke up and went to meet my friend where he was lying down.
I said, “I want to see T.B. Joshua”.
He asked me, “For what?”
I said, “If you don’t show me, I will kill you now”.
I said that I would kill him and his blood would represent for his prophet.
He said that he did not know anything but that he is hiding under his umbrella.
I said, "Under his umbrella. Connect me, I want to talk to him".
That was how he linked me. I called and somebody picked up the call.
I said, "Please, I want to speak to the Prophet".
The person said that I could not talk to the Prophet but I could give him the message.
I gave my message.
Later, the person called me and said that the man of God said that I should come the following morning.
That was how I came.
We can see on the screen how our sister was receiving her deliverance.
She said she made a phone call. As many of us may remember, during the deliverance the evil spirit said that
they called, she called the prayer line and she came.
We give glory to God Almighty for the wonderful deliverance that took place.
When I came and he called me, I wanted to fight but I found that I could not fight.
There was fire all over by body – my palms, legs, everywhere.
I did not believe there was something like deliverance because I have gone to many places for deliverance
and many men of God and at the end, they would turn and befriend me.
They would start asking me out.
Some of them would tell me to bring 50 000 or 10 000 naira and I was somebody who did not have a job.
I concluded that there were no genuine men of God, that church business was business.
It was in the SCOAN that I knew that there is still deliverance,
that some men of God still have the power of God in them.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Glory to God.
Finally madam, now that you are delivered, what are the changes in your life?
How have you been sleeping since your deliverance? What can you say?
Before I was delivered, I could sit here and see all over the world.
That day I sat, I could not see anything.
No more eating in my dreams or swimming and no more crown.
I am happy. When I sleep, I sleep and wake up normal.
Glory be to God.
Finally, now that you are delivered, what is your advice to viewers around the world watching you right now,
about what Jesus Christ can do in people's lives?
My advice goes to ladies out there
who are not content with what they have or what their husbands give them.
They would see another person and want to be like that person
but you don’t know the kind of spirit that possesses that person.
You say in school, "Please, can you lend me that thing?"
When you take and wear it, you are already possessed.
I want to advise women all over the world to be content with what they have.
For women who are looking for the fruit of the womb,
don’t go to any spiritualist who will take you to a river and give you a child.
They would say they want to baptise you
but they are initiating you and also the child they would give you.
At the end, that child will bring hypertension to you or kill you.
Wait for the time of the Lord.
It is God who gives children who will not give you sorrow.
There is no other power. The devil does not have power to give children.
Everything that the devil gives is fake.
It is only God that gives original things.
And for men...
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!